Finding Aid for the Centennial History Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Medical Center - Hospital - Public Service (Box 0025, Folder 23)
- Medical School - Administration (Box 0025, Folder 24)
- Medical School - Administration - Dean Robinson, G. Canby (Box 0025, Folder 25)
- Medical School - Administration - Dean Goodpasture, Ernest W. (Box 0025, Folder 26)
- Medical School - Administration - Dean Batson, Randolph (Box 0025, Folder 27)
- Medical School - Administration - Deans (Box 0025, Folder 28)
- Medical School - Administration - Finance (Box 0025, Folder 29)
- Medical School - Administration - Finance - Commonwealth Fund (Box 0025, Folder 30)
- Medical School - Administration - Finance - Federal Aid (Box 0025, Folder 31)
- Medical School - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0025, Folder 32)
- Medical School - Changing Status (Box 0025, Folder 33)
- Medical School - Changing Status - Reorganization 1909-1925 (Box 0025, Folder 34)
  folder empty. correspondence, etc. J. H. Kirkland and General Education Board
- Medical School - Changing Status - Regionalism Hospitals (Box 0025, Folder 35)
- Medical School - Changing Status - Town and Gown (Box 0025, Folder 36)
- Medical School - Changing Status - University Center (Box 0025, Folder 37)
- Medical School - Changing Status - 1961 (Box 0025, Folder 38)
- Medical School - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0025, Folder 39)
- Medical School - Curriculum - Late 19th Century - Local Context - Medical and Health Conditions in Nashville (Box 0025, Folder 40)
- Medical School - Curriculum - Late 19th Century - Origin and Proprietary Period (Box 0025, Folder 41)
- Medical School - Curriculum - Flexner Report (Box 0025, Folder 42)
- Medical School - Curriculum (Box 0025, Folder 43)
- Medical School - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0025, Folder 44)
- Medical School - Curriculum - 1973 (Dr. Allan Bass) (Box 0025, Folder 45)
- Medical School - Curriculum - Library (Box 0025, Folder 46)
- Medical School - General - Organizations and Histories (Box 0025, Folder 47)
- Medical School - General (including Medical School Curriculum General and Medical School Education General (Box 0025, Folder 48)
- Medical School - Faculty - Faculty Salaries (Box 0025, Folder 49)
- Medical School - Faculty (Box 0025, Folder 50)
- Medical School - Faculty (Box 0025, Folder 51)
- Medical School - Faculty - Dr. Amos Christie (Box 0025, Folder 52)
- Medical School - Faculty - Faculty Research - Including Dr. Earl Sutherland (Box 0025, Folder 53)
- Medical School - Miscellaneous - Manual of Style (Box 0025, Folder 54)
- Medical School - Miscellaneous - Purpose (Box 0025, Folder 55)
- Medical School - Miscellaneous - Tennessee Laws (Box 0025, Folder 56)
- Medical School - Public Service (Box 0025, Folder 57)
- Medical School - Public Service - Tape of Speeches by Chapman and Bass (Box 0025, Folder 58)
- Medical School - Students (Box 0025, Folder 59)
- Medical School - Students - Student Activities (S. C. A. and Fraternities) (Box 0025, Folder 60)
- Medical School - Students - Student Finance (Box 0025, Folder 61)
- Medical School - World War I (Box 0025, Folder 62)
- Medical School - World War II (including R. O. T. C.) (Box 0025, Folder 63)
- Nursing School - Accreditation (Box 0025, Folder 64)
- Nursing School - Administration (Box 0025, Folder 65)
- Nursing School - Administration - Deans (Box 0025, Folder 66)
- Nursing School - Administration - Finance (Box 0025, Folder 67)
- Nursing School - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0025, Folder 68)
- Nursing School - Curriculum (Box 0025, Folder 69)
- Nursing School - Curriculum - Admission and Degree Requirements (Box 0025, Folder 70)
- Nursing School - Reorganization 1924-1927 (Box 0025, Folder 71)
- Nursing School - Miscellaneous (Box 0025, Folder 72)
- Nursing School - Miscellaneous - History (Box 0025, Folder 73)
- Nursing School - Public Service (Box 0025, Folder 74)
- Nursing School - Students (Box 0025, Folder 75)
- Nursing School - General (Box 0025, Folder 76)
- Public Service (Box 0025, Folder 77)
- Public Service - Missions (Box 0025, Folder 78)
- Public Service - Missions - Lambuth, Walter Russell (Box 0025, Folder 79)
- Public Service - Continuing Education (Box 0025, Folder 80)
- Public Service - Health Coalition (Box 0025, Folder 81)
- Miscellaneous (Box 0025, Folder 82)
  material was loose in the box
- Students - Bickman Analysis, 1928 (Box 0025, Folder 83)
- Students - Miscellaneous material (Box 0025, Folder 84)
- Students - George S. Clifford's Diary, 1877 (Box 0025, Folder 85)
- Students - Quotas (Box 0025, Folder 86)
- Students - Prepared Team Paper Controversy (Box 0025, Folder 87)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intramurals (including coed) (Box 0025, Folder 88)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - To 1970 (Box 0025, Folder 89)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Administration - Athletic Staff - Purdy (Byrd Brief) (Box 0025, Folder 90)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Administration - Athletic Staff (Box 0025, Folder 91)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Administration - University Supervision - Physical Plant (Facilities) (Box 0025, Folder 92)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Administration - University Supervision (includes VU and Peabody Cooperation) (Box 0025, Folder 93)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - All Miscellaneous Clippings, including Hustler Special 11/5/71 (Box 0025, Folder 94)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Conferences (Box 0026, Folder 1)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Finances (Box 0026, Folder 2)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Miscellaneous (including Spirit) (Box 0026, Folder 3)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Physical Education (Box 0026, Folder 4)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Recruiting (Box 0026, Folder 5)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Sarratt's File (Box 0026, Folder 6)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Sarratt's Speeches (Box 0026, Folder 7)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Basketball (Box 0026, Folder 8)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Baseball (Box 0026, Folder 9)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Football (Box 0026, Folder 10)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Club Sports (including Lacrosse, Fencing, Soccer) (Box 0026, Folder 11)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Football Stahlman Papers (Box 0026, Folder 12)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Tennis (Box 0026, Folder 13)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Intercollegiate Water Sports (Swimming and Water Polo) (Box 0026, Folder 14)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - Kramer Chart and Brief on Finance (Box 0026, Folder 15)
- Students - Activities - Athletics - General (Box 0026, Folder 16)
- Athletic Association (Box 0026, Folder 17)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities (Box 0026, Folder 18)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Housewright Brief (Box 0026, Folder 19)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - 1950 Controversy (Box 0026, Folder 20)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Black (Box 0026, Folder 21)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Changing Status (Box 0026, Folder 22)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Disorders (Box 0026, Folder 23)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Housing (Box 0026, Folder 24)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Policy (Box 0026, Folder 25)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Regulations (Box 0026, Folder 26)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Rush (Box 0026, Folder 27)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - UGO (Box 0026, Folder 28)
- Students - Activities - Fraternities and Sororities - Women's Panhellenic Council (Box 0026, Folder 29)
- Students - Activities - Literary Societies - Housewright Brief (Box 0026, Folder 30)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - Student Christian Association (SCA) and Religious Emphasis Week, 1943 (Box 0026, Folder 31)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - Impact (Box 0026, Folder 32)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - Impact 1967 (Box 0026, Folder 33)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous (Box 0026, Folder 34)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - Glee Club, Choir, Chorus, Music (Box 0026, Folder 35)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - Hazing (Box 0026, Folder 36)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - VISTA (Box 0026, Folder 37)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous - WRVU (Box 0026, Folder 38)
- Students - Activities - Publications and Publications Board (Box 0026, Folder 39)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Salmon Briefs (carbons) (Box 0026, Folder 40)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Austral (Box 0026, Folder 41)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Hustler (includes the McGrath Brief) (Box 0026, Folder 42)
- Students - Activities - Publications - The Jade (missing) (Box 0026, Folder 43)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Love (Box 0026, Folder 44)
- Students - Activities - Publications - On (volume I), Prometheus, The Style of the Place (Box 0026, Folder 45)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Private Poetry Review (Box 0026, Folder 46)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Vandy Vampire (Box 0026, Folder 47)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Versus (Box 0026, Folder 48)
- Students - Activities - Publications - Visions, The West End Journal (volume I number I of each) (Box 0026, Folder 49)
- Students - Attitudes (Box 0026, Folder 50)
- Students - Attitudes - Athletics, 1971 (Box 0026, Folder 51)
- Students - Attitudes - Criticism of the University, 1934 (Box 0026, Folder 52)
- Students - Attitudes - Political (Box 0026, Folder 53)
- Students - Attitudes - Racial (Box 0026, Folder 54)
- Students - Attitudes - Religious (Box 0026, Folder 55)
- Students - Awards (Box 0026, Folder 56)
- Students - Coeds (Box 0026, Folder 57)
- Students - Coeds - Equal Rights (Box 0026, Folder 58)
- Students - Coeds - Kate Lupton (Box 0026, Folder 59)
- Students - Coeds - McGaw Report, 1971 (Box 0026, Folder 60)
- Students - Coeds - Nashville College for Young Ladies (Box 0026, Folder 61)
- Students - Disorders (Box 0026, Folder 62)
- Students - Disorders - Hazing (Box 0026, Folder 63)
- Students - Faculty and Student Relations (Box 0026, Folder 64)
- Students - Faculty and Student Committees (Box 0026, Folder 65)
- Students - Faculty and Student Relations - Student Task Force on Tenure (Box 0026, Folder 66)
- Students - Finances (Box 0026, Folder 67)
- Students - Negro - Hustler articles, 1974 (Box 0026, Folder 68)
- Students - Freshmen (Box 0026, Folder 69)
- Students - Freshmen - 1972 Information (Box 0026, Folder 70)
- Students - Freshmen - 1971 Information (Box 0026, Folder 71)
- Students - Freshmen - Year Profile 1968-1972 (Box 0026, Folder 72)
- Students - Health (Box 0026, Folder 73)
- Students - Negro (including items from RG 20) (Box 0026, Folder 74)
- Students - Honorary Societies (Box 0026, Folder 75)
- Students - Negro - Publication (Box 0026, Folder 76)
- Students - Placement (Box 0026, Folder 77)
- Students - Regulations (Box 0026, Folder 78)
- Students - Regulations (Box 0026, Folder 79)
- Students - Residences - Report of the Commission on Student Housing (Box 0026, Folder 80)
- Students - Residences (Box 0026, Folder 81)
- Students - Residences - 1948 (Box 0026, Folder 82)
- Students - Self-Government - Community Affairs Board (CAB) (Box 0026, Folder 83)
- Students - Self-Government - Political Organizations (Box 0026, Folder 84)
- Students - Self-Government (Box 0026, Folder 85)
- Students - Self-Government - Honor System (Box 0026, Folder 86)
- Students - Statistics, 1875-1960 (Box 0027, Folder 1)
- Students - Statistics - Reports of the University Registrar, 1967-1968 through 1975-1976 (Box 0027, Folder 2)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous (Box 0027, Folder 3)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Arts (Box 0027, Folder 4)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Campus Ministry (Box 0027, Folder 5)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Clippings from Minutes (Box 0027, Folder 6)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - History (Box 0027, Folder 7)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Histories (Box 0027, Folder 8)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Honorary Degrees (Almanac, Fall 1972) (Box 0027, Folder 9)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Nashville, 1970 (Box 0027, Folder 10)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Purpose (Box 0027, Folder 11)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Visitors (Box 0027, Folder 12)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Twenty-Fifth Anniversary (Box 0027, Folder 13)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Class Day (1913) (Box 0027, Folder 14)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Commencement 1882, 1924 (Box 0027, Folder 15)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - J. H. Kirkland's Fortieth Anniversary (Box 0027, Folder 16)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Commencement 1972, 1973 (Box 0027, Folder 17)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Founder's Day (Box 0027, Folder 18)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Tennessee Centennial Exposition (Box 0027, Folder 19)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Fiftieth Anniversary (Semi-Centennial) (Box 0027, Folder 20)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Seventy-Fifth Anniversary (Box 0027, Folder 21)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Fiftieth Anniversary Banner Articles (Box 0027, Folder 22)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Centennial (Box 0027, Folder 23)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Centennial - Local Press (Box 0027, Folder 24)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Centennial - Hustler (Box 0027, Folder 25)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Centennial - Speeches (Box 0027, Folder 26)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Celebrations - Centennial - Descendants of Commodore Cornelius Vanderbilt (Box 0027, Folder 27)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - University Press (Box 0027, Folder 28)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - Publications (Box 0027, Folder 29)
- Vanderbilt University - Miscellaneous - University Publications Partial List (Box 0027, Folder 30)
- Wars and Military - AROTC, NROTC and Students (including Awards) (Box 0027, Folder 31)
- Wars and Military - General (ROTC) (Box 0027, Folder 32)
- Wars and Military - ROTC (Box 0027, Folder 33)
- Wars - Spanish American (Box 0027, Folder 34)
- Wars - World War I (Box 0027, Folder 35)
- Wars - World War I - Alumnus (Box 0027, Folder 36)
- Wars - World War I - General - SATC (Box 0027, Folder 37)
- Wars - Military - AROTC - World War I (Box 0027, Folder 38)
- Wars - World War II (Box 0027, Folder 39)
- Wars - World War II (McKee Brief) (Box 0027, Folder 40)
- Wars - World War II - Alumni (Box 0027, Folder 41)
- Meeting of Vanderbilt University Chapter April 24, 1973 (2 cassette tapes) (Box 0027, Folder 42)
  tape 1: Questions answered by Dr. Chapman and Dr. Bass; tape 2: Speech of Dr. Allan Bass; Questions
- Wars - Vietnam - Statements by Chancellor Alexander Heard (Box 0027, Folder 43)
- Wars - Vietnam - Faculty Attitudes (Box 0027, Folder 44)
- Wars - Vietnam - Military Training AROTC, NROTC (Box 0027, Folder 45)
- Wars - Vietnam - Students (Box 0027, Folder 46)
- Wars - Vietnam - Students - Attitudes (Box 0027, Folder 47)
- Wars - Vietnam - General (Box 0027, Folder 48)
- Divinity School Quadrangle Pre-Dedication Program (Box 0027, Folder 49)
- Divinity School - Administration - Finances (Box 0027, Folder 50)
- Divinity School - Administration - Physical Plant (Box 0027, Folder 51)
- Divinity School - Administration - Dean Tillett (Box 0027, Folder 52)
- Divinity School - Changing Status (Box 0027, Folder 53)
- Divinity School - Related Schools and Institutes -Atlanta Theological Seminary; Disciples of Christ Foundation (Box 0027, Folder 54)
- Divinity School - Curriculum - Entrance and Degree Requirements Brief (Box 0027, Folder 55)
- Divinity School - General - Curriculum (Box 0027, Folder 56)
- Divinity School - Curriculum - 1972-1973 (Box 0027, Folder 57)
- Divinity School - Miscellaneous - Purpose (Box 0027, Folder 58)
- Divinity School - Miscellaneous - Governance (Box 0027, Folder 59)
- Divinity School - Miscellaneous - Haun, Charles Interview (Box 0027, Folder 60)
- Divinity School - Miscellaneous - Documents (including Promotional Material re: Rural Church School) (Box 0027, Folder 61)
- Divinity School - Public Service (Box 0027, Folder 62)
- Divinity School - Related School and Institutes - Correspondence School and Biblical Institute (Box 0027, Folder 63)
- Divinity School - Students - Correspondence re: Chao Tze Ch-en (Box 0027, Folder 64)
- Divinity School - Students - Attitudes (Box 0027, Folder 65)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Duplicate Material (Box 0027, Folder 66)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Telegram - Drs. Christie and Scott to H. S. Vanderbilt 10 June 1960; Reply 12 June 1960 (Box 0027, Folder 67)
- Divinity School - Students - Women (Box 0027, Folder 68)
- Divinity School - Students - Activities - Pearson Letters (Box 0027, Folder 69)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson (Box 0027, Folder 70)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Branscomb on Lawson (Box 0027, Folder 71)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Foster, Arthur L. - Chronology of Events (Box 0027, Folder 72)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Information From Chancellor's files, I-44, Kirkland Hall (Box 0028, Folder 1)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Information from Chancellor's Files, Miscellaneous II, Kirkland Hall (Box 0028, Folder 2)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Information from Stahlman Papers (Box 0028, Folder 3)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - BJ and Executive Committee Minutes, 1960 (Box 0028, Folder 4)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Important Papers - Chancellor's Files - Kirkland Hall (Box 0028, Folder 5)
- Divinity School - General - Miscellaneous Histories (Box 0028, Folder 6)
- Divinity School - General - Miscellaneous History (Aydebtt Brief) (Box 0028, Folder 7)
- Divinity School - Administration - Deans (Box 0028, Folder 8)
- Divinity School - Faculty (Box 0028, Folder 9)
- Divinity School - Faculty - Publications - Oriental Series (Box 0028, Folder 10)
- Divinity School - Faculty - Shipp, Alfred M. - Attack on McTyeire, June 1885 (Box 0028, Folder 11)
- Divinity School - Miscellaneous - History (Tillett, Thompson, Bard) (Box 0028, Folder 12)
- Divinity School - Administration - Dean Harrelson (Box 0028, Folder 13)
- Divinity School - Students (Box 0028, Folder 14)
- Divinity School - Students - Lawson - Readmission (Return) 1969-1971 (Box 0028, Folder 15)
- Administration - Physical Plant - Magruder Calendar (Box 0028, Folder 16)
- Changing Status - Discontinued Schools - Dental (Ray brief) (Box 0028, Folder 17)
- Changing Status - Discontinued Schools - Pharmacy (Glen brief) (Box 0028, Folder 18)
- College of Arts and Science - Curriculum (Byrd brief) (Box 0028, Folder 19)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty (Byrd brief) (Box 0028, Folder 20)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty (Glen brief) (Box 0028, Folder 21)
- College of Arts and Science - Faculty (Glen brief) (Box 0028, Folder 22)
- College General - Education General - c.1830-80 (McKee brief) (Box 0028, Folder 23)
- College General - Students - Activities (Byrd's briefs) (Box 0028, Folder 24)
- College General - Administration - Presidents (Hood brief) (Box 0028, Folder 25)
- College General - Curriculum - Academic Curricula of American Universities in 1876 (Post brief) (Box 0028, Folder 26)
- Divinity School - Curriculum - Brief (Box 0028, Folder 27)
- College General - Changing Status - University Center (Hood brief) (Box 0028, Folder 28)
- Engineering School - Miscellaneous - History (Kramer brief) (Box 0028, Folder 29)
- Engineering School - Miscellaneous - History (Kramer brief) (Box 0028, Folder 30)
- Engineering School - Miscellaneous - History (Kramer brief) (Box 0028, Folder 31)
- Graduate School - Administration (Hood brief) (Box 0028, Folder 32)
- Graduate School - Curriculum - Degrees (Degree and degree requirements - McKee brief) (Box 0028, Folder 33)
- Graduate School - Curriculum (Courses - McKee brief) (Box 0028, Folder 34)
- Establishment - Law School (Briefs, section of first draft) (Box 0028, Folder 35)
- Law School - Curriculum - Library (including preliminary brief) (Box 0028, Folder 36)
- Medical School - Miscellaneous (Hood brief) (Box 0028, Folder 37)
- Nursing School - Miscellaneous - History (Post brief) (Box 0028, Folder 38)
- Nursing School - Miscellaneous - History (Post brief) (Box 0028, Folder 39)
- Nursing School - Miscellaneous - History (Post brief) (Box 0028, Folder 40)
- Nursing School - General - Miscellaneous - History (Post brief) (Box 0028, Folder 41)
- Student - Self-Government (McKee brief) (Box 0028, Folder 42)
- Students - Activities - Publications (Salmon brief) (Box 0028, Folder 43)
- Students - Activities - Miscellaneous (Byrd brief) (Box 0029, Folder 1)
- Students - Activities - Athletics (Kramer brief) (Box 0029, Folder 2)
- Students - Activities - Athletics (Kramer brief) (Box 0029, Folder 3)
- Students - Activities - Athletics (Kramer brief) (Box 0029, Folder 4)
- Students - Activities - Athletics (Kramer brief) (Box 0029, Folder 5)
- Student - Self-Government - Honor System (McKee brief) (Box 0029, Folder 6)
- Wars - Vietnam (McKee brief) (Box 0029, Folder 7)
- Wars/Military - ROTC (McKee brief) (Box 0029, Folder 8)
- Wars - Post World War II and Korea (McKee brief) (Box 0029, Folder 9)
- Wars - Spanish American and World War I (McKee brief) (Box 0029, Folder 10)
- Public Service - Missions (Glen brief) (Box 0029, Folder 11)
- Centennial History - Outline and Organization (abridged outline sent to A.H.) 1971-73 (Box 0029, Folder 12)
- Centennial History - Table of Contents, Aids and Guides (Box 0029, Folder 13)
  pulled from a three ring binder
- Centennial History Business - Termination Correspondence, Receipts, etc. (Box 0029, Folder 14)
- Centennial History Business - Staff, 1976-77 - Samuels, Essie W. (Box 0029, Folder 15)
- Centennial History Business - Staff, 1976-77 - Swint, Henry Lee (Box 0029, Folder 16)
- Centennial History Staff - Housewright, Mrs. Barbara J. - Retired (Box 0029, Folder 17)
- Harris, James Clay - Retired (Box 0029, Folder 18)
- Centennial History Staff - Bryan, Ed - Retired (Box 0029, Folder 19)
- Centennial History Business - Correspondence/Publication - Jones, McGaw, Matthew, Branscomb, Beach, et.al. (Box 0029, Folder 20)
- Centennial History Business - Correspondence/Heard, Alexander (Box 0029, Folder 21)
- Centennial History Business - Initial Business (Box 0029, Folder 22)
- Bibliography of Specific Articles in Periodicals and From Reference Works (Box 0029, Folder 23)
  3x5 index cards organized in a microfilm box
- Bibliography Cards (Box 0029, Folder 24)